

M. Hassan Zaheer

Data Scientist

How to reach me:

Primary Cell:

0348-0236400

Secondary Cell:

0333-2396938

Email:

mhassanzaheer@gmail.com

Linkedin:

@mhassan-zaheer

Adress:

Amina square, Garden East, Karachi

Professional Skills

Flutter App Development,
API Integration, Firebase, Flask,
C#, JavaScript, HTML/CSS,
Python, SQL, Data Scraping,
Graphic designing Automation,
Machine learning, Programming,
Data Modeling, Client Handling,
Data Analysis, Data
Management, Data Analytics,
Data Visualization · Data
Science, Project Management.

Personal Profile

Data Scientist with a BSCS degree and two years of experience in the relevant field. Skilled in machine learning, data analysis, automation and Power BI dashboarding. Seeking to apply my expertise and creativity in the computer science Field.

Career Summary

Senior Analyst

Dec 2021 - Present

EY (Ernest & Young)

- Efficient production planning and Automation of a Production Plant.
- Developed and deployed finance models to optimize business processes.
- Designed interactive dashboards on Power BI
- Developed user-friendly interfaces.

Data Analyst Intern

Feb 2021 - Aug 2021

Frontier Technology Institute

- Web scraping and product development.
- Worked on some concepts which include:
 - Data pre-processing
 - Data Analytics
 - Automation
 - API Integration
 - Freelancing

Educational Training

PAF - KIET

BS-CS, Jan 2019 - Jan 2023

- CGPA: 3.73 / 4.00
- Electives: Machine Learning, Information Security
- Awarded the Directors
 Honor Award for academic excellence.
- Developed an app for medical diagnosis as a final year project.
 - Used ML and DL models to predict based on the input data.
 - Integrated APIs from various sources.
 - Hosted the model on the cloud.

Certifications

Flutter App Development

Jawan Pakistan Aug. 2021- Mar. 2021

Web Development

Skill Development Council Feb. 2021- Aug. 2021

Graphic Animation Program

Skill Development Council Sept. 2020- Apr. 2021

Data Science

Frontier Technology Institute Jan. 2021- Jun. 2021

Software engineering

NED University Nov. 2019- May. 2020

Manager (Analytics) at EY Cell: 0300 8295271